# **AARON BOOTH**

**Phone**: (704) 962-9817 • **Email**: <u>abooth9422@gmail.com</u> • Charlotte, NC 28227 **Github**: <u>https://github.com/ABooth9422</u> • **Portfolio**: <u>https://abooth9422.github.io/</u>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abooth9422/

### SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer with over a decade of experience in Retail Management and a dedication to learning new technologies. Effective at combining creativity and creative problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among staff and peers for strong determination and attention to detail when executing projects.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

# Languages:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React.js, Node.js, C#, .Net, Database Theory, Bookshelf.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, and Git

## **PROJECTS**

**Tattoo4**U | **Github**: github.com/ABooth9422/Project1 | **Site**: abooth9422.github.io/Project1 | **Full Stack Developer** Tattoo4U is an application that is designed to connect users with design styles in surrounding tattoos shops.

- Worked in a group of four creating JavaScript for the API call and the front-end development.
- Technologies and skills used: CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Mapquest API, Yelp API, Google Firebase

### EXPERIENCE

Technical Support / Hardware Installer Netsafe Solutions

March 2019 - Present

Charlotte, NC

Daily responsibilities are to ensure that all customers' networks are operational if stationed at the help desk.

Key Accomplishments:

- Increased sales by 20% with on-site installs.
- Top Customer satisfaction rating from customer tickets

## Addition Experience

Assistant Store Leader April 2017 - March 2019

Petsmart RockHill, SC

General Manager May 2013 - April 2017

PartyCity Charlotte, NC

#### **EDUCATION**

Bootcamp Certificate: UNCC, Charlotte, NC

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, HandelbarsJS & ReactJS.